<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sonaar</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="i_accept">I accept</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="start">Start using SONAAR</string>
    <string name="page_5_text">By using SONAAR, you are agreeing to allow SONAAR to collect the text descriptions of the images that you tweet on Twitter or post on Facebook. SONAAR does not collect any identifying information, only the image and the text description.</string>
    <string name="page_4_text">Access denied! In order to send the screenshot to our database, SONAAR needs access to your gallery of images.</string>
    <string name="page_3_text">In order to send the screenshot to our database, SONAAR needs access to your gallery of images. SONAAR will ask for that permission next.</string>
    <string name="page_1_text">SONAAR is a service that helps you create accessible content on you social networks (currently supported social networks are Twitter and Facebook)</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_1">When SONAAR detects that you are tweeting or posting an image, you will receive a notification with a proposed text description of the image that you can use in your tweet or post.</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_2">To be able to achieve this, SONAAR needs to take a screenshot of your phone, crop it to the image size and send it to our server. There we search for the image. If we already have it we don\'t even store it, but we will be able to send you any descriptions we have stored. If we don\'t have it, we store it, generate a description and send it to you. When you complete your post or tweet we store any description you created so that it can help other users in the future.</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_3">By clicking \"I Accept\", you are agreeing with this collection</string>
    <string name="consent" translatable="false">consent</string>
    <string name="uuid" translatable="false">uuid</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="notification_text">SONAAR detected that you are posting a image to %1$s. A possible altText to your image is: %2$s. Please consider add it to your image post. %3$s</string>
    <string name="notification_text_twitter">To do so click on the +Alt button.</string>
    <string name="notification_text_twitter_2">To add an altTex to your post, click on the +Alt button.</string>
    <string name="notification_text_facebook">To do so publish the image, then open it and click on the more button (3 dot button) and select "Edit alt text".</string>
    <string name="notification_text_facebook_2">To add an altTex to your post, publish the image, and then open it and click on the more button (3 dot button) and select "Edit alt text".</string>
    <string name="notification_text_none">SONAAR found a possible altText to your image: %1$s</string>
    <string name="notification_text_alt_not_found_none">SONAAR could not find an altText, but automatically generated some concepts about the image: %1$s</string>
    <string name="notification_text_alt_not_found">SONAAR detected that you are posting a image to %1$s. We could not find an altText, but automatically generated some concepts about the image: %2$s. %3$s</string>
    <string name="please_activate_the_sonaar_service_on_the_accessibility_settings_menu">Please start or restart the SONAAR service on the accessibility settings menu.</string>
    <string name="soonar_is_active">SONAAR is already active.</string>
    <string name="go_to_accessibility_settings">Go to accessibility settings</string>
    <string name="image_not_found">SONAAR was not able to find an image.</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
    <string name="show_less">Show less</string>
    <string name="report_problem">Report a problem</string>
    <string name="help_us_improve">Help us improve</string>
    <string name="revoke_consent">Revoke consent</string>
    <string name="revoke_consent_summary">This will revoke the permission to take screenshots</string>
    <string name="delete_screenshots">Delete all screenshots</string>
    <string name="delete_screenshots_summary">This will delete all screenshots on your phone</string>
    <string name="screenshot_handling">Screenshots handling</string>
    <string name="alt_text_upload">Alt text upload</string>
    <string name="alt_text_upload_summary">Ask for consent to share alt text with SONAAR</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="sent">Sent</string>
    <string name="see_more">See more</string>
    <string name="copy_clipboard">Copy to clipboard</string>
    <string name="click_on_one_item_to_copy_it_to_the_clipboard">Click on one item to copy it to the clipboard</string>
    <string name="alt_text_by_sonaar">: alt text by sonaar</string>
    <string name="read_doc">Read documentation</string>
    <string name="doc_url">http://www.di.fc.ul.pt/~cad/SONAAR/documentation/doc.html</string>
    <string name="the_screenshot_will_be_taken_in">The screenshot will be taken in:</string>
    <string name="sending_information_to_sonaar">Searching sonaar for alt texts…</string>
    <string name="error_read_screenshot">Sonnar could not read the screenshot</string>
    <string name="launch_permission_dialog">Launch permission dialog</string>
    <string name="permission_refuse">Permission refused, you have to allow the storage permission on app info menu</string>
    <string name="study_1"><![CDATA[We are looking for participants in a <a href="http://www.di.fc.ul.pt/~cad/SONAAR/recruitment.html">study</a> to help us improve SONAAR and the quality of image descriptions on the internet.]]></string>
    <string name="study_2"><![CDATA[If you wish to participate please <a href="https://forms.office.com/pages/responsepage.aspx?id=AIX6C_KxZkW68W9ZNwiT5yY5gSqckrxFolbQyc5XHrFUNDU2M0gwMEJGWDhWSzZRRFFEODNYODJCQS4u">fill out this form</a>]]></string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong with your request, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="language_not_supported" translatable="false">Your phone language is not supported by SONAAR. All the content will be displayed in english but the app may be unstable.</string>
</resources>