<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sonaar</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="i_accept">I accept</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="start">Start using SONAAR</string>
    <string name="page_5_text">By using SONAAR, you are agreeing to allow SONAAR to collect the text descriptions of the images that you tweet on Twitter or post on Facebook. SONAAR does not collect any identifying information, only the image and the text description.</string>
    <string name="page_4_text">Access denied! In order to send the screenshot to our database, SONAAR needs access to your gallery of images.</string>
    <string name="page_3_text">In order to send the screenshot to our database, SONAAR needs access to your gallery of images. SONAAR will ask for that permission next.</string>
    <string name="page_1_text">SONAAR is a service that helps you create accessible content on you social networks (currently supported social networks are Twitter and Facebook)</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_1">When SONAAR detects that you are tweeting or posting an image, you will receive a notification with a proposed text description of the image that you can use in your tweet or post.</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_2">To be able to achieve this, SONAAR needs to take a screenshot of your phone, crop it to the image size and send it to our server. There we search for the image. If we already have it we don\'t even store it, but we will be able to send you any descriptions we have stored. If we don\'t have it, we store it, generate a description and send it to you. When you complete your post or tweet we store any description you created so that it can help other users in the future.</string>
    <string name="page_2_text_3">By clicking I Acceptyou are agreeing with this collection</string>
    <string name="consent">consent</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
</resources>